Meika Freckelton

0452634523



meikafreckelton@gmail.com



Meika Freckelton



MeikaFreckelton



ameikafreckelton



meikafreckelton.github.io

Experience

Work

- KFC Team Member Mar 2015 - Oct 2015
- Subway Sandwich Artist Jan 2016 - Sep 2016
- Oct 2016 - present

Education

Caroline Chisholm College

Glenmore Park: 2012 - 2018

Tafe NSW

Ultimo: Feb 2018 - Dec 2018

- Certificate III in Design Fundamentals (Fashion)
- Certificate IV in Fashion Design

Tafe NSW

Nepean: Feb 2019 - Dec 2019

Diploma of Graphic Design

Coder Academy

Online/Ultimo: Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

Diploma of Information Technology

About Me

I am studying full-stack web development at Coder Academy, where I am currently learning the MERN stack. In the two years prior, I studied fashion design and then graphic design. During my graphic design course, I found a new love for coding through HTML and CSS and I just couldn't get enough, so I took a leap and went for it and have only fallen more in love since! I love to solve problems, and previously, that just meant solving visual design problems, however, development now challenges me in a different and exciting way and the sheer satisfaction of both areas is motivating and rewarding to me.

My hobbies









Exercise

Reading

Time in the sun

Meditation

Tech Stack && Tools

mongoDB

Express



































Projects

Ruby Terminal Game

A terminal command line game made with Ruby.

RoR Pet Marketplace App

A two-way marketplace for rescue animals to be adopted, created with Rubvy on Rails.

Halloween Pong

A recreation of the game pong made in an Express Hackathon.

Portfolio

Portfolio site made with HTML and Sass/CSS.

Birthday Facts

A site created during a JavaScript hackathon which prints historical facts based on a date input.

Dev Social Media

My first full-stack MERN application, created with a partner which acts as a platform for devs to socialise, share their ideas and get noticed.